Ibrahim Samadzada

LinkedIn | GitHub

Location: Azerbaijan, Baku Email: isamadzada@gmail.com | Mobile: +994558863884

FLUTTER DEVELOPER

As a passionate **Flutter developer** with over **1 year and 2 month** experience, I am seeking opportunities to further develop my skills in this field. I am dedicated to expanding my knowledge and expertise in Flutter and am enthusiastic about the potential for growth in this area.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages : Dart,JavaScript,TypeScript
Frameworks : Flutter,React Native,Nest
Libraries : Bloc,Provider,Redux

Dev Tools : Visual Studio Code, Git, BitBucket, Gitlab

EXPERIENCE

FLutter-React Native Developer

Feb 2023 – Apr 2023 Remote – Wilmington,DE

Code and Care

- Developed dynamic, responsive and cross-platform mobile applications in a team using Flutter
- Worked with **REST APIs** to retrieve and display data from databases
- Worked on new features as Voice-memo and Image uploading

Flutter Developer

Aug 2022 – Jan 2023

Full time – Azerbaijan, Baku

Digital Legion

- Developed dynamic, responsive and cross-platform mobile applications as solo developer using Flutter
- Worked with **REST APIs** to retrieve and display data from databases
- Implemented Subscription and Payment system
- Implemented Chat system to let User write messages to Jasper AI

FLutter Developer

Jan 2022 – Jun 2022

Full time – Azerbaijan,Baku

The Javachip

- Developed dynamic, responsive and cross-platform mobile applications as solo developer using **Flutter**
- · Worked with REST APIs and WebSockets to retrieve and display data from databases
- Implemented **Pedometer logic** to track user's steps
- Implemented Real-time chat to let user's chat with each other

EDUCATION

French-Azerbaijani University

Azerbaijan,Baku

Bachelor in Computer Science

2020 - 2024

Université de Strasbourg *Bachelor in Computer Science*

France, Strasbourg

2020 - 2024

PROJECTS

2Walk Flutter, Bloc Play Market

- Developed a clean and modern mobile application using Flutter
- Maintained business logic using **Bloc**
- Utilized **Responsive design** to ensure compatibility across all devices
- Implemented **Pedometer** to track user's steps

ToDo Flutter, Cubit GitHub

• Developed a clean and modern mobile application using Flutter

- Maintained state management using Cubit
- Utilized Responsive design to ensure compatibility across all devices
- Implemented Local Database enabling the storage of user tasks directly within the phone's memory.

AlZodiac Flutter, Provider GitHub

- Developed a clean and modern mobile application using Flutter
- Maintained state management using **Provider**
- Utilized Responsive design to ensure compatibility across all devices
- Implemented Chat system to let User write messages to Jasper Al

LANGUAGES

Azerbaijani : Native language **Russian** : Second Native

English : C1